(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
遥か昔、天界は
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed...
光と秩序の神々によって統治されていた。
...by the Gods of Light and Order.
人界、魔界、
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm,
そして天界。
and the Heavenly Realm...
全ての境界は、悠久の時を刻む
...all worlds were kept in balance...
「銀の湖」によってその均衡が保たれていた。
...by the celestial lake of Ginn.
聖なる「法」により、何者もその湖に立ち入ること、
A sacred "law" forbade any from entering the lake
あるいは穢すことは禁じられていた。
or sullying its waters.
Long ago, the Heavenly Realm was governed
by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm,
and the Heavenly Realm.
All worlds were kept in balance
by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred "law" forbade any from entering
the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days
joyfully in the heavens.
A mischievous girl, today too
she was chasing after her friends,
playing pranks and teasing them.
She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day... Weather like this
really makes me want to sing!
せまいせまいあなぼこで
Inside a cramped, narrow hole
夢を見せあうぼくたちは
The two of us show each other our dreams
あの世もこの世もいられない
We can't be in that world; neither can we be in this world
ああ神様 子どもの神様
Dear God, child god
ぼくらはあなたの遊んだ
We are in your sandbox,
砂場の中ですり傷だらけです
covered in scratches
タタタ･･･
Ta-ta-ta...
踊るよ 回るよ
We're dancing, we're spinning
僕らの踊りはおかしな踊り
Our dance is a strange dance
踊ったつもりで 笑ったつもりで
Intending to dance, intending to laugh
倒れたつもりで 叫んだつもりで
Intending to collapse, intending to shout
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
Eyes are dizzy, sounds are mushy
足もふらふら まもるしふにゃふにゃ
Feet are dizzy, protective charms are mushy
太陽も月も 空も神様も生み出して
The sun and the moon, the sky and the gods, all born
あなぐらぐらしは抜け出せない
Hole-dwelling is inescapable
抜け出せない 抜け出せないから
Can't get out, because we can't get out
抜け出さない
So we don't get out
抜け出さないからお目々閉じて
So we don't get out, close your eyes
2 1 0
ああ 落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆくよ
Falling, falling, falling away
あなぐらぐらしのうそのなか
Inside the vortex of "Hole-Dwelling"
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆくよ
Falling, falling, falling away
いっしょになかよくどこまでも
Together, getting along, everywhere
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
きみとぼくとはいつまでも
You and I, forever
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Same, same, isn't it the same?
いけない いけない
It's forbidden, it's forbidden...
さみしい さみしい
it's lonely, it's lonely.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's fall away
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, just the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Oh no, oh no, I'm lonely, I'm lonely
なかま なかま あなたはいかが？
Friends, friends, how about you?
なかま なかま ぼくらはなかま
Friends, friends, we are friends
あなたはなかま？ 合言葉？
Are you a friend? The password?
あなぐら世界の合言葉？
The password to this hole-dwelling world?
抜け出せない 抜け出せない
I can't get out, I can't get out
抜け出せないから教えない
I can't get out, so I won't tell you
あなたはなかま？ さみしいなかま
Are you a friend? A lonely friend
奈落に生きるなかまですか
Are you a friend living in the abyss?
夢のかけらを飲んでいる
I'm drinking down fragments of dreams
きみの夢もまぜまぜして
Mixing in your dreams as well
あの世もこの世もいられない
I can't stay in that world, or this one
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
My eyes are spinning, sounds are all wobbly
腕もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
My arms are spinning, illusions are all wobbly
太陽も月も 空も神様も
The sun, the moon, the sky, even God
ギトギトに 鮮やかで
Are all greasy and vivid
抜け出せない 抜け出せない
I can't get out, I can't get out
抜け出せないから抜け出さない
I can't get out, so I won't leave
抜け出さないからお目々閉じて
Since I'm not leaving, close your eyes
閉じて 閉じて 閉じて...
Close them, close them, close them...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's fall away
あなぐら暮らしの渦の中
In the vortex of hole-dwelling life
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's fall away
一緒に仲良くどこまでも
Getting along together, forevermore
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, just the same?
きみと僕とはいつまでも
You and I, for all eternity
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, just the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Oh no, oh no, I'm lonely, I'm lonely
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Fall, fall, let's fall away
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Aren't we the same, the same, just the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
Oh no, oh no, I'm lonely, I'm lonely
サンタマリア 起死回生の一打を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, give us a miraculous comeback strike
湿っぽいのはいらんな 爽快に派手にやって終い
We don't need anything damp, let's do it flashily
そんな答えは 自問自答の向こう側
That kind of answer is on the other side of self-reflection
嫌になっちゃうな しょうがない アンダーグラウンドな世界の中
It's annoying, but it can't be helped in this underground world
井の中の蛙 大会優勝者 未練たらたら エステ
The frog in the well, the tournament winner, lingering with regrets... EST
熱中自尊心なんて到底ないな
I have absolutely no obsessive self-esteem
愛を歌っては愛されたことない 未体験回答
Singing of love, yet never loved; an inexperienced response
毎度退場障害 耐え難い 正反対でいたい
Exit obstacles every time, it's unbearable; I want to be the exact opposite
別に不満などないけれど
I have no particular complaints,
描いた夢と違うけれど
though it's different from the dream I drew.
なぜか心に穴が空いたようだ
For some reason, it's as if there's a hole in my heart.
気づいてしまうから
Because I realize it,
ありきたりな人生に
To this ordinary life,
今ピリオドを打て
put a period to it now.
混ざり合うようなこの気持ちが
This feeling that seems to blend together,
抑えようもない衝動が
this uncontrollable impulse,
望み通り叶わない現実になって
it becomes a reality that doesn't go as hoped,
まだまだくたばってなんかないぜ
but I'm not dead and gone just yet.
神に誓ってないと想え
Know that I haven't sworn to any god,
実体のない将来に果て見て
looking at the end of a formless future.
騒ぐ心の内を聞こう
Let's listen to the noise within our hearts,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so we don't fade away between dreams.
足を止めていられぬよう
So that we cannot stop in our tracks,
コロロン 甘い声放（ほう）
Kororon, let out a sweet voice.
言葉では何とでも言える 此処が正念場
You can say anything with words; this is the climax.
そう 野外は愛のないディスカッション アテにやっていけ
Yeah, handle the loveless outdoor discussions.
その結果が全てなんだ 嬉し難いが
That result is everything, though it's bittersweet.
千載一遇だ まだ生かしてくれよ 世界の中
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance; let me live on.
定かではないが まだ僕の中には
I'm not sure, but inside me still remains
数多余す事のない事実が
countless undeniable facts.
泥に飼い慣らされるこの毎日が
These days of being tamed by the mud...
嫌 食べられてしまい
No, I'll end up being devoured.
実は不安しかないけれど
Actually, I'm filled with nothing but anxiety,
描いた夢もないけれど
and I have no dreams either.
だから心に穴が空いたようだ
That's why it feels like there's a hole in my heart.
気づいてしまった
I've realized it now.
ありきたりな人生に 今ピリオドを打て
Put a period to this ordinary life now.
混ざり合うようなこの気持ちが
This feeling that seems to blend together,
抑えようもない衝動が
this uncontrollable impulse,
望み通り叶わない現実になって
it becomes a reality that doesn't go as hoped,
まだまだくたばってなんかないぜ
but I'm not dead and gone just yet.
神に誓ってないと想え
Know that I haven't sworn to any god,
実体のない将来に果て見て
looking at the end of a formless future.
騒ぐ心の内を聞こう
Let's listen to the noise within our hearts,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so we don't fade away between dreams.
足を止めていられぬよう
So that we cannot stop in our tracks,
コロロン 甘い声放（ほう）
Kororon, let out a sweet voice.
Yay! Woo!
Thank you so much for coming everyone to my 3D live.
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English,
and we have Sora-senpai!
こんそらめー！ Hello! I'm Tokino Sora!
Kon-sora-me! Hello! I'm Tokino Sora!
Kronii, Happy Birthday!
Thank you!
Very gorgeous outfit!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Oh man, look at the stage here.
Very beautiful.
Ah, so pretty! Look at the night sky!
綺麗！ Wow...
Beautiful! Wow...
Oh man...
Oh, Kronii, Kronii. Why did you invite me
to your birthday live?
Oh, uh, well, last year, we hung out together
a bit and I had a lot of fun.
So I wanted to invite you
and get to sing together.
I thought that would have been really great,
so thank you for coming!
Thank you! Yay!
I... so I love you!
Oh my god! Love is such a strong word...
I, I love you too.
I want to go to... uh, udon eating with you!
I want to go to... udon eating with you!
Oh, udon!
Yeah!
Yeah! Let's go eat! Oh my god!
We'll get anything! What kind of udon?
I like anything!
Me too!
Anything? Yeah, I like anything.
あ、他には？
Ah, anything else?
Ah, you know, there's like cold udon
and then there's just like udon with like soup
and then there's like onsen tamago and all that.
おお、いろいろあるね！
Oh, there are many varieties!
Hey! Yes! So like, many!
なんでも大丈夫。なんでも大丈夫。
Anything's fine. Anything's fine.
あ、じゃあ一緒にあの dinner... I'm going to dinner.
Then, let's go to... dinner together. I'm going.
Oh, dinner! Yeah!
Oh my god, that would be really good. Yeah!
Whoo! Yay!
そしてそして、あ、サプライズの、あ、ハッシュタグ。
And then, and then, um, surprise my um hashtag.
Oh yeah, if you guys haven't already checked it out
...right there #krorigin.
#krorigin?
Yeah!
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag.
Um, it's going to be awesome, absolute cinema.
And so yeah, keep on the lookout for
Fallen Grace.
Whoo! Yay!
Thank you so much for coming. あ、本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for coming. Thank you very much.
え、こちらこそありがとう。これからも仲良くしてね。
No, thank you. Let's continue to be friends.
Yeah! あ、それなら嬉しいです。Yay!
Yeah! Ah, I'd be happy with that. Yay!
大好きなフレンドだから。
Because you're a dear friend.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Wow. Stop.
Thank you! Thank you! Yay! じゃあ、またね！
Thank you! Thank you! Yay! Well, see you later!
Thank you! Congratulations! I thank you! Yay!
残響散歌
Zankyou Sanka
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Who is the phantom flower that blooms on the sleeve?
ただ そこに藍を落とした
I just dropped my indigo dye over there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when the colors dissolve gaudily
銀朱の月を添えて
With the moon of silver vermilion added
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind like rolling
躓くごとに強くなった
I got stronger with each stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部 抱きしめて
Embracing all the light, pain, and anger
選ばれなければ
If you're not chosen,
選べばいい
then it's fine to choose
声よ 轟け
Voice, echo
夜のその向こうへ
beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
Resonate to the scenery so far away
あんなに遠くの景色まで響き渡れ
that was blurred by tears
何を奏でて？
What are you playing?
誰に届けたくて？
Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to remain uncertain
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings
どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how long the struggle
歌と散れ 残響
Sing and scatter, reverberation
ただ一人舞う千夜
Dancing alone through a thousand nights
違えない帯を結べば
If I tie the sash correctly
派手な色も負かす様に
To outshine even gaudy colors
深紅の香こそあわれ
The deep crimson scent is so touching
この先どんなつらい時も
From now on, no matter how hard it gets
口先よりも胸を張って
I'll puff out my chest instead of just talking
抱いた夢の灯を全部辿るだけ
Just following all the lights of the dreams I held
逃げ出すため
Not for the sake of running away
ここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
did I come this far, right?
選ばれなければ
If you're not chosen,
選べばいい
then it's fine to choose
声を枯らして 燃える花のように
With a withered voice, like a burning flower
闇間を照らしたら
If it lights up the darkness
曖昧過ぎる正解も
Even answers that are too ambiguous
譜面にして
I'll turn them into a musical score
夜を数えて 朝を描くような
Counting the nights, like drawing the morning
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
I'll play a vivid sound
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regret
どんなに高い限界も
No matter how high the limit
掻き消して 残響
Erase them, reverberation
In the heavenly realm, there is a Lake of Light
that controls all worlds,
and Kronii would always observe
the human worlds from there out of curiosity.
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
a desire grew within her to visit not only the heavenly realm...
...but also the human world,
where she could talk to people and play tricks on them.
I want to go down to the human world.
I want to play some pranks.
バグ
Bug
迷子 迷子 真っ只中 さあ
I'm lost, lost, right in the middle, now
パ パ パ ラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra-paranoia
ギコギコ MY HEART 剪定
Pruning my heart with a buzz-buzz
パ パ パ ラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra-paranoia
退路 退路 断って
Cutting off, cutting off the escape route
絡まった パ パ パ ラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Tangled up, pa-pa-pa-ra-paranoia
SAD SAD 突っ伏して
SAD SAD, prostrate
パ パ パ ラ パーラノーイ「ド」
Pa-pa-pa-ra-paranoi-de
さあ バババグ さバグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bu-bug-bug
タ タ タグ 才能のタグ
Ta-ta-tag, tag of talent
もう ハハハハ グ
Already, ha-ha-ha-ha-bug
感情はハグ
Emotions are a hug
発症 苦しいわ イェイ イェイ イェイ
Painful outbreak, yay yay yay
イェイ イェイ イェイ
Yay yay yay
混ぜ 夜中 泥中 パラノーイア
Mixed midnight, mud paranoia
踊れ 叫べ 挙げろ ワーオ
Dance, scream, raise your voice, wow
混ぜ 大体 詰めろか 闇雲に
Blindly fill it up
凍え 夢々 イェイ イェイ イェイ
Freeze, never, yay yay yay
さあ バババグ さバグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bu-bug-bug
惑わすな イェイ イェイ イェイ
Don't let me be misled, yay yay yay
さあ バババグ さバグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bu-bug-bug
壊れあれ イェイ イェイ イェイ
Be broken, yay yay yay
イェイ イェイ イェイ
Yay yay yay
ぐるぐる バカんけ 予定待って
Round and round, bakanke, wait for the schedule
無理 ズルズル せーので 回れ
Impossible, dragging on, all at once, turn
ぐるぐる バカんけ やっぱ無理
Round and round, bakanke, as expected, impossible
あんこに 草 ピー
LOL at the red bean paste, pi
エンドレス闇
Endless darkness
駄子 駄子 いらない子
Bad kid, bad kid, unwanted kid
パ パ パ ラ パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra-paranoia
良い子 良い子 頑張れぬ反面
Good kid, good kid, on the other hand can't work hard
アドミニ 全てだ あー
Admin is everything, ah
混ぜ 夜中 泥中 パラノーイア
Mixed midnight, mud paranoia
左 右 行き先も ぐるぐる
Left, right, destination is also spinning
非情 限界の 狂っちゃって 闇雲に
Heartless, at the limit, gone crazy, blindly
闇に酔い酔い 否 否 ば
Drunk in darkness, no no
全力 夜中 泥中 パラノーイア
Full power, midnight, in the mud, paranoia
溺れ 叫べ 挙げろ ワーオ
Drowning, screaming, raise your voice, wow
混ぜ 大体 詰めろか 闇雲に
Blindly fill it up
凍え 枯れ果て イェイ イェイ イェイ
Freeze, withered away, yay yay yay
さあ バババグ さバグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bu-bug-bug
乱れあれ イェイ イェイ イェイ
Be in disorder, yay yay yay
さあ バババグ さバグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bu-bug-bug
汚れあれ イェイ イェイ イェイ
Be stained, yay yay yay
否 否 否 イェイ イェイ イェイ
No no no, yay yay yay
この世で造花より綺麗な花は無いわ
There's no flower in this world more beautiful than an artificial one
何故ならば総ては嘘で出来ている
That's because everything is manufactured from lies
Antipathy world
絶望の雨は あたしの傘を突いて
The rain of despair pelts my umbrella
湿らす前髪と心の裏面
Dampening my bangs and the back of my heart
煩わしいわ
It's deceptive
いつしか言の葉はとうに枯れ切って
Before I knew it, the leaves of words had already withered away
言の実はあたしに売れている
The fruit of words is selling to me
鏡に映りそう 描いて
As if reflected in the mirror, I draw
自らを見失ったメイク
The makeup that lost sight of myself
パパパパパパパパ
Pa-pa-pa...
謎 謎 数えて遊びましょう
Riddle, riddle, let's count and play
タタタタタタタタ
Ta-ta-ta...
何故 何故 ここで踊ってるのでしょう
Why, why, are we dancing here?
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't even understand simple things
あたして何だっけ?
What was I again?
それすら夜の手に 絆されて
Even that, bound by the hand of the night
愛のように
Like love
消え 消え
Fading, fading
さよならも言えぬまま なんて
Without even being able to say goodbye
フォニー フォニー フォニー
Phony, Phony, Phony
嘘に絡まっている
I'm entangled in lies
あたしはフォニー
I'm phony
Antipathy world
いつの間にか
Before I knew it,
空の願い嫌になって
the empty wishes became unbearable.
色の眼鏡
Tinted glasses...
貴方を説いてる
are explaining you.
鏡に映る私を抱いて
Hugging the me reflected in the mirror,
誰しもが見間違ったフェイク
everyone misidentified the fake.
どうして
Why...
愛なんてものに群がり それを欲して生きるの
do they flock to love and live only desiring it?
だけ
Just that.
今日も泳いでいる 夜の電車が通り過ぎていく
I'm swimming as the night train passes by.
踊りを貸せよ
Lend me your dance.
なぞなぞ 騙して歌いましょう
Riddle, let's trick and sing.
なぜ なぜ ここが痛むのでしょう
Why, why does it hurt here?
散々な日々は通らないわ
The terrible days won't pass.
絶望の雨は止まないわ
The rain of despair won't stop.
さようならもう言えぬまま泣いた
I cried, unable to say 'goodbye' anymore.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony.
嘘に絡まっている
Entangled in lies.
簡単なことも解らないわ
I don't even understand simple things.
私って何だっけ
What was I again?
それすら夜の手(て)に絆(ほだ)されて
Even that is captivated by the hands of night,
愛のように
just like love.
さようならまたねと呟いた
I muttered, 'Goodbye, see you later.'
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony.
嘘に絡まっている 私はフォニイ
Entangled in lies, I am phony.
造花だけが知っている秘密のフォニイ
The secret phony only the fake flowers know.
Lately I realized
I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know?
Do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree?
Oh hey
I can feel the rain wash over us
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down / 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I got to make a move, make a move
So far I cannot break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side
we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
way to you
Can't make them stop
hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk
all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side
and my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive
it goes like
Oh hey
I can feel the rain wash over us
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down / 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice...
I got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side
we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too
Side by side
we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
way to you
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world
Goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world
and cause mischief grew.
And so, she broke the rules
and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake
drew the attention of the Heavenly Guardians,
who snared and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
I was just interested in humans
and... just wanted to talk.
きっと手をつなぐだけで
Just holding hands surely
ゾッとされる
makes them shudder.
馬鹿げた競争一抜けたら
If you drop out of the stupid race,
通報される
you get reported.
突然変異じゃない
I'm not a mutant;
ただの僕さ
I'm just me.
Xとか Yとか
Whether that's X or Y.
べき論者様は
The moralists...
善悪多頭飼い
keep both good and evil.
僕が君を「侵害」する
They're spreading rumors that I'm "violating" you,
って言いふらしてる
they keep saying it.
Oh...
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て
Wearing different clothes
君の前では男子のフリを
Pretending to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand
迎えにきて下さい
Please come to pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone who doesn't even know my face,
僕はもうヴィラン
I am already a villain
Oh 蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ
Oh, snake-scorpion life, snake-scorpion life
挙句の果ての
And at the very end...
糜爛
erosion
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Hiding my deviant nature once again
雄蕊と雌蕊じゃ立ち行かないの
It doesn't work with just stamens and pistils
ねえ知ってんのか
Hey, do you know?
乱歩という作家のことを
About the author called Ranpo?
Import you Import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers eventually bear fruit
ぶるってんじゃねーよ
Don't you be shaking
多種多様の性
A wide variety of genders
愛しい 良い 話をしようか
Shall we have a lovely, pleasant chat?
ゼラチン質の
Of a gelatinous nature...
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
可能性に幸あれ
Good luck to the possibilities
僕のハート 1LDK くらいはさせてよ
Let my heart be at least a 1LDK
Hi there モットー YOLO
Hi there, motto is YOLO
淫靡愛でいいのに
Even lewd love would have been fine
誰も知らない 知られたくない
Nobody knows, I don't want them to know
皮膚の下
Beneath the skin
素晴らしき悪党共へ捧げる唄
A song dedicated to all the wonderful villains
骨まで演じ切ってやれ悪辣に
Play the part to the bone, maliciously
残酷な町ほど
The more cruel the town,
綺麗な虹が立つ
the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Pop-style love dancing in vulgar advertisements
Mr.Crazy Villain Villain
Mr. Crazy Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て
Wearing different clothes,
君の前では男子のフリを
pretending to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand
ここだよ
I'm here
顔も知らない誰かにとって
To someone who doesn't even know my face,
僕はもうヴィラン
I am already a villain
ヴィラン ヴィラン...
Villain, villain...
蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ
Snake-scorpion life, snake-scorpion life
挙句の果ての
And at the very end...
糜爛
erosion
Man... I don't know why I'm here.
I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess.
I should be treated like one.
Ah... man, this sucks.
Go away.
La dee da dee da dee da dee da... da!
Oh, what nice weather today!
Actually, no, I don't know if it's nice weather.
Hello? Oh, hello! Hi!
What is a beautiful blue woman doing here?
In a cage?
This is a gazebo! It kind of looks like a gazebo at first.
Yeah, it's a gazebo.
Well-deserving for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Oh yeah? Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah, I mean, my beauty is pretty telling, so.
Oh... well, yeah, you know, you're decent.
Decent?!
Yeah, yeah, I can see, I can see the goddess vibes.
But I don't know, that's a little disrespectful.
I've never heard this before.
Oh really?
Yeah, I mean, look who you're talking to.
Oh, okay. Who... who are you?
Who do you think you are to be talking...
You don't even deserve to know my name. No.
What?! You're in a cage!
Excuse me? You're like in prison!
No, you just said gazebo!
It's not a cage! It's a gazebo!
No, it's a cage!
If it's a gazebo then get out of the gazebo then!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo?!
Because I'm weak! For now.
Oh, you're weak?
You seem bad, like you did something naughty, didn't you?
No, it wasn't even that bad.
Ah, but you did do something bad,
and now you're stuck in this gazebo...
with the dead fly or whatever that is.
Hey! It may look like a fly,
but it's... it's like my moral support.
Moral support?
Yes.
No, you can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, you think I have anyone else to talk to?
Oh, so you don't deny that it's a dead fly!
It's... I mean, I mean... or you?
Like, what are you?
Like, what's that little thing on your head?
It's... it's...
It's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?
Maybe you're a fly! Maybe you have wings!
What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I look like a fly?
Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore.
You can stay in there for eternity.
Wait! Hey! Hold on!
Hey, hold on, beautiful woman! Come back here!
Come back here! Yoo-hoo! Hello! Beautiful woman!
Hello, hello. Hi, yeah.
Um, so, if you happen to open this cage...
You know, you can put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
Uh, it can be something else.
Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money?
More valuable than money.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Yes. And something that comes with the price of free is...
Guess! My companionship!
Friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye!
Hey, hey, come on! Okay, maybe for a day!
Hello? For a day!
For a day! For a day! For a day!
Now I look like a lonely ass...
Oh, no! Not the lonely ass!
It's okay, it's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually... I'm an angel.
Uh-huh.
We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Oh... then maybe you should...
Please beg.
If you beg, I'll let you out!
Now beg.
I'm gonna speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to them if you're in this cage!
When I get out of here, you will be fired.
How are you gonna get out without me?
That's the whole point of being in here!
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble?
Or do you want to just free me? You should just free me.
And then maybe I'll beg, or whatever you want.
At the price of my companionship!
I'm breaking the fourth wall! I'm here to let you out!
Just let me out!
Just beg!
It's the magic word! Just a magic word that starts with P!
Pray.
Please! Please! Please!
Finally! Finally! Okay.
Fine, because I'm so kind.
Just one please and it would've been all over.
Okay. Let's go.
It's a big door! It's a big door!
Yeah, it is! You got this!
It's okay, I'm Nephilim! I can do this...
For my beautiful friend! My one-day friend!
Beautiful friend! I will release thee!
Oh my god, you did it!
Whoa! Yay!
How did I bother? Yay!
Why did I bother? Yay! I'm free!
Woo-hoo! Oh, yeah! Let's go!
Good for you!
Give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
You can't even let yourself out? Okay.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's more like it! Put you in your place.
Okay, that was really... okay. I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation!
Well, I think we should celebrate!
Celebrate! Celebrate your freedom!
Yeah, yeah!
Oh, it'll be so good. We're gonna, like...
You're gonna treat me to something, right?
I'll treat you to something afterwards.
And then I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups...
and it'll be wonderful.
I don't even have higher-ups!
You keep saying I have higher-ups.
You never know. Life is surprising.
Really?
Yeah. I'm sure you also have a boss, too.
Yay! Yay!
Ow! Ow! When did you get so strong?
I've been training recently!
Wow! It shows! Yay!
Your hands are so big...
Don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
人を過度に信じないように
I try not to have too much faith in people
愛さないように期待しないように
Not to love, not to have expectations
かと言って角が立たないように
But at the same time, I try not to be confrontational
気取らぬように目立たぬように
I try not to be pretentious, try not to stand out
誰一人傷つけぬように
I try not to hurt anyone
虐めぬように殺さぬように
I try not to bully, not to kill
かと言って角が立たないように
But at the same time, I try not to be confrontational
軽いトークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
Not to forget small talk and lip service
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
Always smiling and showing some charm
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
とやかく言わずにたんと召し上がれ
Don't say this or that, just eat up
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You have to fix your pickiness
頭空っぽそのあとに
After your head is empty
残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains is real
きっと君だって同じこと
Surely even you would do the same
どこかでそっと伺いますが
I'll gently ask you somewhere
演じてるならやばいな
If you're acting, that's bad
無駄に自我を晒さないように
Don't expose your ego unnecessarily
話さないように分からないように
Don't talk, don't let them understand
酔わせて口を閉ざさないように
Don't let them drink and shut their mouths
笑わすよりは笑われるように
Try to be laughed at rather than making them laugh
人をちゃんと敬うように
Respect people properly
崇めるように称えるように
Worship them, praise them
でも決して闇にならないように
But never let it become darkness
ふざけないように
Don't mess around
集団参加の終身刑
Life sentence of group participation
まだへれこへれこ言っちゃって
Still saying things so playfully
あれ前髪調整最強じゃん
Isn't that bangs adjustment the best?
ぶっちゃけどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
To be honest, I say it even though I don't care
毎朝毎晩もう限界
Every morning, every night, I'm at my limit
宗教的社会の集団に
To the group of religious society
順応して発狂しないように
Adapt and try not to go crazy
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
時には孤独な愛を君を汚す
Sometimes lonely love stains you
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
立つ鳥の跡きっとクソの跡
A bird leaving surely leaves a mess
初めはあんなに大層な
At first, it was so grand
大言壮語を並べたが
You lined up big words
いやはやはや好きのうち
Well, while you still like it
いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
Well, but today is the first time
こんなのは君センスあるよ
You have talent for this kind of thing
殺し尽くす季節にビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of killing everything, Bitter Choco Decoration
殺し尽くす気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
With the intent to kill everything, Bitter Choco Decoration
F-U-C-K-Y-O-U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Yearning for the ideal everyone wants
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
個性や情は全部焼き払い
Burn away all individuality and emotion
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Kill your greed and ego and bury them in the earth
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
僕は大人にやっと成ったよママ
I finally became an adult, Mama
明日もきっとこの先も
Tomorrow and from now on, too
地獄は続くどこまでも
Hell will continue everywhere
裸足でどうか今だけは
Please, just for now, with bare feet
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
Keep the feelings from when you were a child
意地を張らずにやってこうぜ
Let's do it without being stubborn
思い出したあの時の
I remembered that time
真面目そうな
That serious-looking...
やっぱいいや
Never mind after all
Oh goodness.
Okay, well, I'm free now.
So I can finally get going.
Woohoo! Yay!
Wait.
I just got out of here.
What... what's going on?
Why?
Don't just stand there, do something!
Ugh...
Oh, what happened?
Oh, what the heck?
Where...
Where are my beautiful clothes?
What? Oh my god!
My... my long luscious hair?
What happened?
I can't...
What is this? I can't even take it off.
I mean, oh god, at least I still look beautiful.
But like, what happened?
Oh man, I don't know what's going on.
What is this place anyway?
嫌
No
残機
Zanki
しょっぱいぜ 初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
It's sour, the first meeting, the encounter that was tasted
自暴自棄です 平均的な正論ナビボ
It's self-satisfaction, a poor logical argument
いらっしゃいませ ニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Welcome, the healthy body I aimed for with extra garlic
劣等感 胃袋満たしてる
Filling my stomach with inferiority complex
優等生 無知なフリして踊っちゃって
Honor student, pretending to be ignorant and dancing
決定です 現状把握しちゃうから中断中
I'll interrupt because I've already grasped the situation
もう譲渡 見せびらかし合いましょ劣等感も
Let's show off that inferiority complex
変えられやしないってわかってるから
You know that you can't change it, right?
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible player, intuition is selfish
求められたなら三者会
If you were needed, try three times
くだらん口喧嘩でマシなんだ
It's trivial, it's better to quarrel
もっと もっと 思い描いた通りに
More, more, just as I imagined
うざいくらい叫んだって
It's noisy, even if you scream...
喰らんだって 譲れない日々よ
Even if you eat it up, these days won't fade away
栄養になって待って汚し合え
Become food, wait and eat each other
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて セクシーなアンジュルボは濁った声で
If you don't understand the remaining lives... The sexy trap is a muddy voice
歌えば感謝です
If you sing, it's gratitude
感謝 感謝 仕方なくて
Gratitude, gratitude, it's inevitable
ソワソワしちゃって
I'm restless
でも気持ちいいな
But I feel good
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
When I get home, I water the plants immediately, the workings of human beings
実のところ恵まれてても今日も虚無感が友達
Even if I'm blessed in reality, today is also an empty friend
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合唱曲
Awaken from sleep, ear-punch, love until you drink it up
仲良しこよしの時間
Time for getting along
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
An incomprehensible player, intuition is selfish
求められたなら三者会
If you were needed, try three times
細かいご指摘も有り難き
I appreciate your detailed feedback
結局 瞳孔開いてんのに
After all, my pupils are wide open
うざいくらい叫んだって
It's noisy, even if you scream...
喰らんだって 譲れない日々よ
Even if you eat it up, these days won't fade away
栄養になって待って汚し合え
Become food, wait and eat each other
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて セクシーなアンジュルボは濁った声で
If you don't understand the remaining lives... The sexy trap is a muddy voice
歌えば感謝です
If you sing, it's gratitude
感謝 感謝 仕方なくて
Gratitude, gratitude, it's inevitable
ソワソワしちゃって
I'm restless
でも気持ちいいな
But I feel good
あたしたちずっと
We are always...
気持ちいいな
I feel good
ただ健やかでいたい
I just want to be healthy
誰にも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I don't want to cause trouble for anyone
戦わないと撫でてもらえない
But if I don't fight, I won't get a pat on the head
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear
うざいくらい叫んだって
It's noisy, even if you scream...
喰らんだって 譲れない日々よ
Even if you eat it up, these days won't fade away
栄養になって待って汚し合え
Become food, wait and eat each other
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて セクシーなアンジュルボは濁った声で
If you don't understand the remaining lives... The sexy trap is a muddy voice
歌えば感謝です
If you sing, it's gratitude
言いたいことジャンケン
Janken for what I want to say
ご愛顧じゃ
Thanks for the patronage
まずは質感湧くまで拵え
First, prepare it until the texture comes out
すぐ吐けなくて 呆気なくて セクシーなアンジュルボは潮の匂いで
I can't throw it up immediately... The sexy trap is the smell of the tide
耐えて感謝です
I'm grateful for enduring
やり返したいし 啜り喰らうわ くだらないことで笑いたかった
I want to get back and slurp it up, I wanted to laugh at trivial things
願いじゃ満たされないほど
So much that my wishes cannot be fulfilled
暴れるのは今に始まったことじゃないけど
Going wild is nothing new, but...
私たちセッションで絶好調で健康で
We are in great shape and healthy in the session
気持ちいいな
I feel good
アイデンティティ
Identity
あ、ちょっと君に伝えたい
Ah, wait a moment, there's something I want to tell you
何かがあったような
There's something going on
けったい真逆の踊るベール
That bizarrely inversed dancing veil
サカサマだと知って
is upside down
好意とは魅惑のプログラム
Goodwill is a fascinating program
さてさて差し詰めここから行き着くは
Simply put, what comes from here is...
愛 愛
Love, Love
アイデンティティ
Identity
それは嗜好のアイデンティティ
That is the identity of taste
アイデンティティ
Identity
唸れ 君一人のせい
Groan, it's all your fault
まだ捨てないで待って
Don't throw it away yet, wait
それは一つ二つのデスティニー
That is one or two destinies
繋げてハッピー
Connect them, happy
落ちる流れ星と
Falling, the falling flow star and...
歪なあの星な
the distorted, the distorted, that star
ラララララ
La la la la la
重なる面影に寄り添う
Snuggling up to the overlapping presence
そっと君に寄り添う
Softly, snuggling up to you
弾けだす視界胸に飛び込む
Springing out, the view that jumps into the chest
刻むあなたの
Carving your...
アイデンティティ
Identity
フランギプライド 飛び込めデンジャラス
Frangi-pride, dive into dangerous
さっと羽ばたく 強気の狂気と
Quickly taking flight, with a confident madness
そんで裏切り お涙頂戴
And then betrayal, a plea for sympathy
ララララララララ
La la la la la la la la
ランブラララと 足取りデンジャラス
Run-bla-la-la, with dangerous footsteps
背後隠れた 二人にフォーカス
Focusing on the two hidden behind
やっと見つけた 不思議な正体
Finally found the mysterious true form
ララララララララ
La la la la la la la la
きっと恋とは
Surely love is...
真逆のプログラム
an opposite program
ただ
Just...
差し詰めここから
ultimately from here,
行き着くは
where I arrive is...
愛、
Love,
アイデンティティ
Identity
それは希望のアイデンティティ
It's the identity of hope
アイデンティティ
Identity
唸れ
Groan,
君一人のせい
it's all your fault
まだ捨てないで待って
Don't throw it away yet, wait
それは一つ二つのデスティニー
It's a one or two-part destiny
すぐさまハッピー
Instant happiness
落ちる流れ星と
With the falling shooting star
歪なあの星
and that distorted star
重なる面影に寄り添う
Nestling close to the overlapping shadows
そっと君に寄り添う
Gently nestling close to you
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込む
The bursting vision dives into my chest
ハート
Heart
刻むあなたの
Carving your...
アイデンティティ
Identity
And now, it's time
for our special guest to appear.
Um, Wata-mama, please come in!
Yeeeaah! Whoo!
誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Yay!
Um, I was hoping to have Wata-mama appear at this year's birthday celebration,
so I tried to reach out and, uh, she accepted, and I'm so happy!
Yay!
お花が咲いた時はすごいびっくりしたんだけど、
I was really surprised when the flowers bloomed,
今日はすごい誕生日の素敵な日なので、
but today is a wonderful birthday day,
ここに来れてとっても嬉しいです。おめでとうございます！
so I'm very happy to be here. Congratulations!
私も嬉しいです。
I'm happy too.
来てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming.
Yay!
And um, since we have this opportunity,
can I ask Wata-mama some questions?
うん、いいよ。
Yeah, sure.
Um, like let's say... hmm... what's your favorite food?
あんこです。
It's anko.
And then?
あんこです。
It's anko.
Only anko? Oh, okay.
嘘、嘘だけど。
Lie, I'm just kidding.
いっぱいあるけど、あんこが一番好きです。
There are many, but I like anko the best.
Ah, okay. I'm gonna keep that in mind
for next time.
In that case, oh, I have one more question.
Um, what kind of game do you like?
えっとね、 えっと RPG と、
Well, um, RPGs and...
えっと、 ローグライクのゲームが好きです。
um, I like roguelike games.
アクションが苦手。
I'm bad at action games.
あー、 ゲーマーですね。
Ah, a gamer, I see.
でも簡単なのが好きです。
But I like simple ones.
Ah, so nice. And um, oh yeah, I have some exciting news
to share together with Wata-mama!
Yay!
And please take a look at this! Pow!
Whoo! Yay!
And we have so much this time too.
It's going to be so awesome.
And this illustration was drawn none other than Wata-mama!
書きました！
I drew it!
She's so talented. Oh my god, so happy.
Um, was there a theme or like a particular detail
you focused on for this illustration?
法被用のイラストなので、
Since it's an illustration for a happi coat,
ちょっと派手目に、
I made it a bit flashy,
なんかこうでっかく、 みんなが楽しんで着れるような絵にしました。
kind of big, like a picture that everyone can enjoy wearing.
可愛く描けたと思います。
I think I drew it cutely.
めっちゃくちゃ可愛いです。 ありがとうございます。
It's incredibly cute. Thank you very much.
Yay!
Yay! And um, well let's go through the details.
Um, first, we have this! Tada!
Whoo!
あー法被を出しちゃった！
Ah, I released a happi coat!
Yay!
It's the, um, Eternal Kronie Happi...
Design on the back!
And you can show your support. It'll be so cool!
And then we have this next. Tada!
Kronii Love! Button Badge.
Yeah, Sparkly!
And it's a heart-shaped and glittery holographic...
...can badges, and it's gonna be perfect for fan activities.
And you can combine it with the next product,
which is this one!
Yay! It's my Oshi bag!
It comes with a clear window where you can display merch,
like maybe a plushie or the can badge. So keep that in mind.
And then next we have this!
Oh, how cute!
It's based off of my outfit... Divine Chibi Plushie Keychain.
And it's gonna be so exciting!
And then there's a full set purchase bonus.
The limited quantity includes an original card with a handwritten signature,
and then the second one is a bonus voice pack called 'Reminiscence'.
Don't worry, even when those run out, you still get other bonuses,
like original card with foil-stamped replica signature and the voice pack.
Once again, if you want to see the entire summary, here's the full set!
If you're gonna buy, the full set is the way to go, obviously.
And that's all for Ouro Kronii's birthday! Woohoo!
Be sure to buy it, everyone!
And we have even more news! Take a look at this!
The release of my first physical EP 'Way2U' has been officially decided!
Sales will start right away after the stream ends.
And the album contains five tracks!
This includes 'Way2U', 'Storm', 'I'm Human Too',
'Hibiscus', and of course the classic 'Daydream'.
Every song is really special, so I want everyone to listen.
And there's gonna be a CD plus an LP vinyl version,
so maybe you can compare them and see which one you like better.
Plus it comes with a hand-signed poster,
but there's a limited amount, so be sure to check.
Way2U will be released as a digital single on March 15th,
and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight, so don't miss it!
And you can check the description for the sales site.
After this, I'd like to sing one song together with Wada-mama.
I've wanted to sing this song ever since I asked, so I'm really looking forward to it.
So let's enjoy this!
楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's enjoy it!
ギラギラ
Lyrics, Music: てにをは
Gira Gira
Lyrics, Music: Teniwoha
あーもう本当になんて 素晴らしき世界
Ah, truly, what a wonderful world
んで今日もまた 己の醜悪さに惑う
And so, once again today, my own unsightliness confuses me
だのに人を好きって思う
And yet, this feeling of wanting to be loved by another
だのに人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
And yet, this feeling of wanting to love another
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
Is what makes me suffer so
Ugly 正直言って私の顔は
Ugly, honestly, my face is as if
そう神様が左手で描いたみたい
It were drawn by God with His left hand
必然この世にある ラブソングは
Therefore, the love songs in this world...
どれ一つ絶対私向けなんかじゃないでしょ
Not a single one is meant for me, right?
使い道のない口紅
I’m just an unused lipstick
憐れみを恋に欲しいままに
Wanting to keep my pity, as it is
スパンコールの傘 蓋で身を守る
With a sequined umbrella and its lid to protect me
愛されないくらいなんだ
I can’t believe how unlovable I am
ギラギラ
Gira Gira
輝いて私は夜を飲み
Shining brightly, I swallow the night
Rap, tap, tap, tap
今に見てろこの luv
Just you wait, this luv
目に染みるは1ミリグラムの花火
It stings my eyes, a single milligram firework
Drag on, drag on
なんてファニー この世はミザリー
What a funny, this world is misery
ギラギラ
Gira Gira
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown, even before the Buddha knew
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい
It seems I was already sanely mad
それは世界の方か
Is it the world...
それとも私の方ですか？
Or is it me?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Coexistence was impossible from the start
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
Imitations are all the more sorrowful
無我夢中 走る 走る
Frantically running, running
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before the strong acid rain washes it away
蛍光色の痣 抱いて
Embracing the fluorescent-colored bruises
メラメラ
Mera Mera
火を噴いて私は夜の神
Spitting fire, I am the god of the night
Rap, tap, tap, tap
そこで見てろこの luv
Watch it from there, this luv
不夜城なり あなたなりの武装で
Become a sleepless castle with your own armor
Rap, tap, tap, tap
なんてファニー 孤独はガソリン
How funny, loneliness is gasoline
燃料 卑屈な町を行く
Fueling my way through the servile town
目を閉じて
Close your eyes
もういいかい もういいかい
Are you ready? Are you ready?
もしも神様が左利きなら
If God were left-handed
どんなに幸せか知れない
I don't know how happy I would be
ギラギラ
Gira Gira
輝いて私は夜を飲み
Shining brightly, I swallow the night
Rap, tap, tap, tap
今に見てろこの luv
Just you wait, this luv
目に染みるは1ミリグラムの花火
It stings my eyes, a single milligram firework
Drag on, drag on
なんてファニー この世はミザリー
What a funny, this world is misery
ギラギラ
Gira Gira
あー花は満ちて
Ah, now I’m full of flowers
ありのまんまじゃいられない誰も彼も
I can't just be who I am, nobody can
なんて素晴らしき世界だ！
What a wonderful world!
ギラついていこう
Let's go out with a glitter
This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon.